<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authors on Dongshuai</title><link>https://DongshuaiLi.com/authors/</link><description>Recent content in Authors on Dongshuai</description><generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://DongshuaiLi.com/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://DongshuaiLi.com/authors/admin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DongshuaiLi.com/authors/admin/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dongshuai Li is a Postdoctoral Researcher at &lt;a href="https://www.space.dtu.dk/">DTU Space&lt;/a>, currently she is the Principle Investigator(PI) of DFF Sapere Aude Project &lt;a href="https://dff.dk/en/apply/supported-research/research-leaders/research-leader-2023/dongshuai-li">Studying Lightning Processes with Neuromorphic Imaging on Microsecond Time Scales(NEURO-Lightning)&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Dongshuai received her PhD degree from &lt;a href="https://www.nuist.edu.cn/main.htm">Nanjing University of Information Science &amp;amp; Technology (NUIST)&lt;/a>, China in 2016.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>From Oct. 2014 to Sep. 2015, she worked as a research assistant with &lt;em>Dr. Farhad Rachidi&lt;/em> and &lt;em>Dr. Marcos Rubinstein&lt;/em> at &lt;a href="https://www.epfl.ch/labs/emc/">École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne (EPFL) - EMC Lab&lt;/a> in Lausanne, Switzerland.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>From Feb. 2016 to Dec. 2017, she worked as a research assistant with &lt;em>Dr. Fei Liu&lt;/em> at Earth System Modelling Centre and Climate Dynamics Research Centre in Nanjing, China.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>From Jan. 2018 to Dec. 2021, she joined the &lt;a href="https://trappa.iaa.es/">TRAsient Plasmas in Planetary Atomospheres (TRAPPA)&lt;/a> group as a Postdoctoral Researcher at &lt;a href="https://www.iaa.csic.es/en">Instituto Astrofísica Andalucía, IAA-CSIC&lt;/a> in Granada, España. Where she was supervised by &lt;em>Dr. Alejandro Luque&lt;/em>, mainly working on the ERC Project &lt;a href="https://cordis.europa.eu/project/id/681257">Lightning propagation and high-energy emissions within coupled multi-model simulations&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>In 2022, she moved to Denmark at &lt;a href="https://www.space.dtu.dk/">DTU Space, Technical University of Denmark &lt;/a> to work with &lt;em>Dr. Tosten Neubert&lt;/em> and &lt;em>Dr. Olivier Chanrion&lt;/em> as a Postdoctoral Researcher on the Danmarks Frie Forskningsfond(DFF) Project Investigation of Blue Corona Discharges at the Top of Thunderclouds.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>In Nov. 2023, she got the DFF Sapere Aude Project Studying Lightning Processes with Neuromorphic Imaging on Microsecond Time Scales(NEURO-Lightning), where she starts to focus on studying inner plasma physics of lightning by using neuromorphic imaging technique.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Her main research interests cover a wide range of topics related to Atmospheric Science, Lightning Physics, Computational Electromagnetics and etc.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>During her free time, she likes traveling, hiking, camping and kayaking.&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --></description></item></channel></rss>