<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authors on About Me</title><link>http://example.org/authors/</link><description>Recent content in Authors on About Me</description><generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>http://example.org/authors/admin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/authors/admin/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dongshuai Li is a Postdoctoral Researcher at &lt;a href="https://www.space.dtu.dk/">DTU Space&lt;/a>, currently she is the &lt;strong>Principle Investigator(PI)&lt;/strong> of DFF Sapere Aude Project &lt;a href="https://dff.dk/en/apply/supported-research/research-leaders/research-leader-2023/dongshuai-li">&lt;strong>Studying Lightning Processes with Neuromorphic Imaging on Microsecond Time Scales(NEURO-Lightning)&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Dongshuai received her PhD degree from &lt;a href="https://www.nuist.edu.cn/main.htm">Nanjing University of Information Science &amp;amp; Technology (NUIST)&lt;/a>, China in 2016.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>From Oct. 2014 to Sep. 2015, she worked as a research assistant with &lt;strong>Dr. Farhad Rachidi&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>Dr. Marcos Rubinstein&lt;/strong> at &lt;a href="https://www.epfl.ch/labs/emc/">&lt;strong>École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne(EPFL) - EMC Lab&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>From Jan. 2018 to Dec. 2021, she joined the &lt;a href="https://www.iaa.csic.es/en">Instituto Astrofísica Andalucía - Consejo Superior de Investigaciones Científicas(IAA-CSIC)&lt;/a> as a Postdoctoral Researcher in Granada where she was supervised by &lt;strong>Dr. Alejandro Luque&lt;/strong>, working at the ERC Project &lt;a href="https://cordis.europa.eu/project/id/681257">&lt;strong>Lightning propagation and high-energy emissions within coupled multi-model simulations&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>In 2022, she moved to Denmark at &lt;a href="https://www.space.dtu.dk/">Technical University of Denmark (DTU) - DTU Space&lt;/a> to work with &lt;strong>Dr. Tosten Neubert&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>Dr. Olivier Chanrion&lt;/strong> as a Postdoctoral Researcher on the Danmarks Frie Forskningsfond(DFF) Project &lt;strong>Investigation of Blue Corona Discharges at the Top of Thunderclouds&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>In Nov. 2023, she got the DFF Sapere Aude Project &lt;a href="https://neuro-lightning.com/">&lt;strong>Studying Lightning Processes with Neuromorphic Imaging on Microsecond Time Scales(NEURO-Lightning)&lt;/strong>&lt;/a>, where since then she can focused on study inner plasma physics of lightning by using neuromorphic imaging technique.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Her main research contributions cover a wide range of topics related to Atmospheric Science, Lightning Physics and Computational Electromagnetics and etc.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>During her free time, she likes traveling, hiking, camping and kayaking.&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --></description></item></channel></rss>